The respiratory act comprises four phases.
呼吸行為には4つの段階があります。
Therefore, first we learn to...
ですから、まず私たちは...を学びます。
I am conscious of my respiration,
私は自分の呼吸を意識しています。
and then I am conscious of following my respiration.
そして、自分の呼吸を追跡することを意識しています。
First, you bring mindfulness to the respiration.
まず、呼吸にマインドフルネスをもたらします。
Within mindfulness, there is also an energy we call concentration.
マインドフルネスの中には、集中力とも呼ばれるエネルギーも存在します。
Because automatically, I must remain attentive for a longer duration.
なぜなら、自動的により長く注意を払う必要があるからです。
Attempt to perceive this.
それを感じてみてください。
Scientific research indicates that by working at this level,
科学的研究は、このレベルで取り組むことで、
you develop empathic faculties, compassion, and attention,
共感能力、慈悲の心、注意力を発達させ、
far more subtle, which lead to a state of well-being.
はるかに繊細なものとなり、あなたを幸せにします。
What I refer to as joy, when one learns to remain focused on their respiration,
私が喜びと呼ぶもの、それは自分の呼吸に留まることを学ぶとき、
when one learns to follow their respiration,
自分の呼吸を追跡することを学ぶとき、
subsequently, one learns to recognize the body, uniting body and mind,
その後、体を認識することを学び、体と心を統合します。
and then, at the fourth level, one learns to release the body.
そしてその後、第4のレベルは、体を弛緩させることを学ぶことです。
Once this is accomplished, we delve into the essence.
これを終えたら、より深い状態に入ります。
The fifth level is to generate a feeling of joy, which is said to originate from the teachings
第5のレベルは喜びの感情を生み出すことです。これは仏陀の教えに由来すると言われており、仏陀は「私はあなた方に16通りの呼吸を生み出す方法を教えよう」と述べました。
of the Buddha, who stated, 'I will teach you 16 ways to engender respiration.'
そしてその後、呼気行為に重点を置いたブラフマリーと呼ばれる練習を行います。それは蜂の呼吸です。
And then, we will perform an exercise that focuses more on the expiratory act,
それは脳に非常に興味深い能力をもたらし、非常に迅速に心の平静とストレスの軽減をもたらします。
which is called 'Brah-mari,' the bee's breath.
舌は心の芽であり、甲状腺は舌から発生します。
This has a very interesting faculty on the brain, rapidly inducing a calm state
実際、私たちは心で話しますが、それは甲状腺の、周波数的な、ほとんどエネルギー的な繊細さをもって、と言えるでしょう。
of the mind and a reduction in stress.
ある時点で、それはもはや言葉ではなく、音そのものであることを意味します。
The tongue is the bud of the heart, and the thyroid originates from the tongue.
それはあなたが触れる周波数です。
One speaks with their heart, in fact, but with the frequential, almost energetic, subtlety,
私が皆さんを導きます。最初の5つのステップを行い、その後ブラフマリーを行います。
one might say, of the thyroid.
そして弛緩させ、体の中の、ある種の静寂を少し観察します。
This implies that at a certain point, it is no longer the word itself, but the sound.
喉の奥から来る音を出す必要があります。
It is the frequency you engage with.
C'est la fréquence que tu touches.
I will guide you; we will perform the first five steps, then we will do the Brah-mari,
Je vais vous guider, on va faire les cinq premières étapes, puis on va faire le bras-marie,
and then we will release and simply observe a kind of silence within the body.
et puis on va relâcher et on va juste observer un peu un espèce de silence dans le corps.
One will need to produce a sound originating from the posterior pharynx.
Il faudra faire un son qui vient de l'arrière-gorge.
Like a bee or a bumblebee ascending, and this sound must rise into the cavity to
蜂やマルハナバチが上昇するように、この音は腔内に上昇し、
culminate at the level of the sinuses.
副鼻腔のレベルで終わります。
We will assess the entire cerebral region, extending into the tympanic cavity and sinus cavity.
我々は鼓室および副鼻腔まで、全ての脳領域を読み取ります。
Frontal, sphenoidal, maxillary, and even temporal.
前頭骨、蝶形骨、上顎骨、そして側頭骨まで。
We will first adopt an upright posture.
まず、まっすぐな姿勢をとります。
When I straighten my back, upon exhalation, I will experience the true physiological effect
背筋をまっすぐにしたとき、呼気時に真の生理学的効果が得られます。
of a release on my vagal tone.
迷走神経の弛緩です。
this parasympathetic and restorative system.
この副交感神経系と回復のシステムです。
If I position myself thus, and restrict here, I diminish this capacity.
このように姿勢をとり、ここで遮断すると、この能力を低下させます。
I experience this state of inspiratory awareness.
私はこの吸気の意識状態を経験します。
Second level, I am very, very attentive to the act of
第二段階では、私はその行為に非常に注意を払います。
respiration.
呼吸の行為に。
I am aware of the body's movement during the respiratory act.
私は呼吸行為における身体の動きを意識します。
Fourth level, I relax.
第四段階では、私はリラックスします。
I relax upon exhalation, fully conscious that I am inhaling.
私は吸気していることを完全に意識しながら、呼気時にリラックスします。
We will perform twelve respirations.
12回の呼吸を行います。
the first two we will perform thus, and the last ten we will perform with the
最初の2回はこのように行い、最後の10回は
ears slightly occluded; you will place your fingers over your ears
耳を軽く塞ぎ、耳に指を置きます。
to facilitate internal integration; you inhale, and during the
内側へと統合するために、息を吸い込み、そして
expiratory phase, you produce a gentle humming sound.
呼気時に小さなハミングをします。
we inhale, occlude the ears, and you perform this
息を吸い込み、耳を塞ぎ、そして行います。
ten times, and then you may release; you
10回行い、リラックスできます。あなたは
enter into the emerging silence, and within this silence, you
現れる静寂の中に身を置き、そしてその静寂の中であなたは
simply allow a feeling of joy to arise, and
ただ喜びの感情が来るに任せ、そして
if you are unsure what to do, offer a small
何をすべきかわからない場合は、小さな
smile; take another inhalation, perform
微笑みを浮かべ、もう一度吸気を行い、
an exhalation, and at the conclusion of the exhalation,
呼気を行い、そして呼気の終わりに
There is a space where you do not respire.
呼吸しない空間があります。
But you settle your consciousness within this space.
しかし、あなたはこの空間に意識を置きます。
Even as you reinspire, you remain within this space.
再び吸気するときでさえ、あなたはこの空間に留まります。
When you enter this perception, you bring yourself closer
この知覚に入ると、あなたは近づきます
to the embryonic breath.
胚の呼吸に。
Because the embryonic breath was not subject to diaphragmatic movements.
なぜなら、胚の呼吸は横隔膜の動きに左右されなかったからです。
And if you do so, you will begin
そして、もしあなたがそうすれば、あなたは始めるでしょう。
to perceive your heart, which was there eight months
あなたの心臓を知覚し始めるでしょう、それは8ヶ月間そこにありました
and nine days before your thoracic respiration.
そしてあなたの胸式呼吸の9日前から。
In other words, your heart begins to beat after 21 days.
言い換えれば、あなたの心臓は21日後に鼓動し始めます。
And so it is good to place oneself, from time to time, in this silence,
ですから、時々この静寂の中に少し身を置くのは良いことです。
because it is in silence that reorganization can occur.
なぜなら、静寂の中でこそ再編成され得るからです。
This embryonic force is always present, but to enter into
この胚の力は常に存在しますが、その中に入るためには
this presence,
この存在に。
this contact, you must accept to go into silence. You might rediscover
この接触、あなたは静寂の中に行くことを受け入れなければなりません。あなたはもしかしたら見つけるでしょう
a healing movement. Or that health can express itself, flourish more
治癒の動きを。あるいは、健康がより表現され、開花するのを
easily.
容易に。
You place it in this silence and allow space to open. Thus, a need for space.
あなたはそれをこの静寂の中に置き、空間が開くのを許します。つまり、空間が必要です。
If there is no space, there is no development. Therefore, both this
空間がなければ、発達はありません。ですから、この
spacious silence are required. But if you restore to the tissue this
広々とした静寂が必要です。しかし、もしあなたが組織にこの
capacity
能力を再び与えるなら
to rediscover this moment of silence,
この静寂の瞬間を取り戻す
the body knows very well how it should reorganize itself because
体はどのように再編成すべきかを非常によく知っています。なぜなら
there it can utilize
そこでは、それは利用できます
its potential upon which it was created.
それが創造されたその潜在能力を
Therefore, I restore the possibility to the system that it knows,
ですから、私はシステムが知っている可能性を再び与えます
but it is so occupied that it no longer knows.
しかし、それはあまりにも忙しすぎて、もう知りません
I restore this vital principle.
私はこの生命原理を再び与えます
je redonne ce principe vital
je redonne ce principe vital